centibid.com 2012-07-14

# CentiBID - Penny Auctions for brand names iPad, iPhone, MacBooks, PlayStation 3 - Save up to 90%

**Scope:**  
This CentiBID Privacy Statement is applicable worldwide and covers how CentiBID treats personal information collected by us through our website, through CentiBID.com, and offline. It does not apply to those sites that do not display or link to this Privacy Statement or that have their own privacy statements.

By using the CentiBID.com, you read and agree to all the terms and conditions Agreement, including this Privacy Policy, and you consent to CentiBID.com's privacy practices. This includes the use and disclosure of any personal information you have shared with us and its transfer to and storage on our servers.

**Data collection:**  
Furthermore we collect some information automatically from your computer while you browse our sites, such as where you go on the CentiBID.com and what you do there. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-over’s), and methods used to browse away from the page.

When you register on CentiBID.com, we collect and store your e-mail address and a password. When you participate in some of the CentiBID.com services, you may also choose to provide the following personal information:

  * Profile information, including first and last name, date of birth, user name and location

  * Contact information for shipping & billing, email address and phone number

  * Financial information including your credit card information

**Non-personal/Anonymous Information Collection:**  
In some instances, CentiBID.com may collect non-personal (aggregate or demographic) data through cookies, web logs, and web beacons. This information is used to better understand and improve the usability, performance, and effectiveness of the website. Please read the “Cookies” section below for more information.

In addition, by using some of our services, anonymous network information may be transmitted back to us such as: the health of the services and types of devices attached to the network. With this information we can determine how users are interacting with the services, to assist us with improving it, and to provide alerts via the services of available software updates/upgrades.

**Use of Cookies and other Web Technologies:**  
Like many websites, CentiBID.com uses automatic data collection tools, such as cookies, embedded web links and web beacons. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and the address of the website from which you arrived at our website. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer, which is a unique address assigned to your PC by your Internet Service Provider or Information Systems Department on a TCP/IP network) and clickstream behavior (for example, the pages you view and the links you click). These tools help make your visit to our website easier, more efficient and more valuable by providing you with a customized experience and recognizing you when you return.

Our website may include widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the widget. Cookies may also be set by the widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it. Our widget may have an import contacts feature to help you email your contacts. At your request we will search your email address book to help you import your contacts to our website.

**Security of Your Personal Information:**  
CentiBID.com is committed to protecting the Personal Information you share with us. When we transfer sensitive personal data (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.  
We utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its security.

We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.

**Use of Data:**  
We will only use your Personal Information in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your Personal Information is used without your consent. Some of the ways we may use your Personal Information to:

  * Process your orders and deliver the services / products that you have ordered.

  * Keep you up to date on the latest announcements, system enhancements, special offers, and other information, provided that you can edit your marketing preferences at any time as described below. This may occasionally include information from other companies about products and services.

  * Provide support and assistance for our Services, including the provision of security patches (if applicable).
  * Provide the ability to create personal profile areas and view protected content.

  * Provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with shipping and billing information.

  * Provide customer feedback and support.

  * Provide and administer contests, sweepstakes or other marketing or promotional activities on our website.

  * Conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better services to our customers. Your completion of any questionnaires is voluntary.

  * Understand more about you, so we can personalize newsletters and websites to your preferences. For example, allow you the opportunity to request specific information on services that may be of interest to you.

  * Allow you to forward information to another individual, such as a friend or co-worker who you believe is interested in receiving the information. CentiBID.com does not store the personal information of the third party. We use the email address and contact name (if applicable) for the sole purpose of sending a one-time email on your behalf.

  * Measure and improve our sites and services

  * Resolve disputes, address complaints and troubleshoot technical problems

  * Analyze site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports

**Disclosure of personal data:**  
We do not sell, rent, share or trade your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so. We may share your Personal Information within NeoPlex Shopping and Entertainment (“CentiBID.com”)

We may share information with members of the CentiBID.com to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Members of NeoPlex Shopping and Entertainment (“CentiBID”) will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you've requested their services.

We reserve the right to publish the First Name, Last Name and username of winners.

_Service Providers._  We may share your information with service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as maintaining the CentiBID.com and providing related services).

_Special Offers._ _ _ On the CentiBID.com, you may have opportunities to express interest in or register for third-party products and services. If you do, we will provide information about you to the third party to implement your request.

_Feedback._ _ _ We may use survey results for our internal development and market research and share the results with our affiliates, consultants, vendors and service providers.

_Assets._ _ _ As our business evolves, CentiBID.com may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets in connection with a merger, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. In such an event, personal information may be one of the assets transferred.

_Other Disclosures._  We may disclose information when permitted by law or under the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary under applicable law; to comply with legal process served on CentiBID.com; to protect the property or interests of CentiBID.com, its agents and employees; or to protect personal safety or the public.

**Access to and Accuracy of Your Personal Information:**  
We need your help in keeping your Personal Information accurate and up to date. Please notify us of any changes to your Personal Information.

You may have the ability to view or edit your Personal Information online. In order to help prevent your Personal Information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your credentials (for example, email address and password). The appropriate method(s) for accessing your Personal Information will depend on which websites or Solutions you have used. CentiBID.com – You can access and update your profile using the CentiBID Profile Management Tool. In any case if you need any other assistance with your account you can send an email to [](mailto:support@CentiBID.com)[customersupport@centibid.com](mailto:customersupport@centibid.com "customersupport@centibid.com").

**Communication preferences:**  
Each promotional email from us includes instructions on how you can unsubscribe from that particular mailing. You may also unsubscribe from various promotional communications by sending a message using the contact information below. Please be sure to include your name, email address and specific relevant information about the material that you no longer wish to receive to [](mailto:support@bidooka.com?subject=Unsubscribe%20from%20promotional%20offers,%20my%20username%20is)[customersupport@centibid.com](mailto:customersupport@centibid.com "customersupport@centibid.com").

These choices do not apply to the receipt of mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the services in accordance with its terms and conditions.

**Linked Websites:**  
Our website may provide links to other third-party websites and services which are outside our control and not covered by this CentiBID.com’s Privacy Statement. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements posted on these (and all) sites you visit.

**Users data removal**  
Registered users can request us to permanently remove their information from CentiBID.com system after cancelling their membership with CentiBID.

**Questions or comments?**  
We value your opinions. Should you have any privacy-related questions or comments related to this CentiBID.com Privacy Statement, please send an email to [](mailto:support@bidooka.com?subject=Questions%20or%20comments)[customersupport@centibid.com](mailto:customersupport@centibid.com "customersupport@centibid.com").

**Updates to this CentiBID.com Privacy Statement:**  
CentiBID.com may update this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. We will post a notice to this policy and the home page link whenever this privacy statement is materially changed so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Your continued use of the CentiBID.com website after any change will signify and confirm your assent to those changes.

**How to contact us**

Direct Live Chat Support from 09:00-18:00 CST Mon-Fri

Phone:  **1 888 509-6996**

Email: [](mailto:support@centibid.com "support@centibid.com")[customersupport@centibid.com](mailto:customersupport@centibid.com "customersupport@centibid.com")

Mail to: 10777 Westheimer Suite 1100, Houston, Texas 77042.

Our regular business hours are Monday thru Friday, 09:00-18:00 CST.
